[{
    "theme": "Números del 20 al 1 millón",
    "questions": [
        { "question": "20", "answers": ["veinte"] },
        { "question": "21", "answers": ["veintiuno"] },
        { "question": "22", "answers": ["veintidós"] },
        { "question": "23", "answers": ["veintitrés"] },
        { "question": "24", "answers": ["veinticuatro"] },
        { "question": "25", "answers": ["veinticinco"] },
        { "question": "26", "answers": ["veintiséis"] },
        { "question": "27", "answers": ["veintisiete"] },
        { "question": "28", "answers": ["veintiocho"] },
        { "question": "29", "answers": ["veintinueve"] },
        { "question": "30", "answers": ["treinta"] },
        { "question": "40", "answers": ["cuarenta"] },
        { "question": "50", "answers": ["cincuenta"] },
        { "question": "60", "answers": ["sesenta"] },
        { "question": "70", "answers": ["setenta"] },
        { "question": "80", "answers": ["ochenta"] },
        { "question": "90", "answers": ["noventa"] },
        { "question": "100", "answers": ["cien"] },
        { "question": "101", "answers": ["ciento uno"] },
        { "question": "123", "answers": ["ciento veintitrés"] },
        { "question": "200", "answers": ["doscientos"] },
        { "question": "300", "answers": ["trescientos"] },
        { "question": "555", "answers": ["quinientos cincuenta y cinco"] },
        { "question": "999", "answers": ["novecientos noventa y nueve"] },
        { "question": "1000", "answers": ["mil"] },
        { "question": "1100", "answers": ["mil cien"] },
        { "question": "1500", "answers": ["mil quinientos"] },
        { "question": "2000", "answers": ["dos mil"] },
        { "question": "1000000", "answers": ["un millón"] }
    ]
}]
